<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jack Alvarez</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://jackalvarez.me/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jackalvarez.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 22:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 22:55:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paragon Fitwear?</title>
        <description>&lt;h1&gt;Hey again stranger!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my second blog post! I hope you&amp;#39;ve enjoyed looking around so far!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So like I mentioned in my &lt;a href=&quot;http://jackalvarez.me/2015/10/15/First-Blog/&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;About Me&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; post (check that piece out if you haven&amp;#39;t already), I am hugely into fitness and powerlifting.  I want to go more into detail on that aspect of my life in another post because I simply have so much to say about it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what&amp;#39;s the deal with the title of this post??? A couple weeks ago, I had posted a video of one of my lifting PRs (and if you wanna see any of my posts be sure to follow my &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.instagram.com/torchyhd&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;).  After I posted this video, I was contacted through a Twitter DM that some company was wondering if I&amp;#39;d be interested in getting &lt;del&gt;sponsored&lt;/del&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;UPDATE: Note that I had to update this blog post to reflect the new changes happening with the Paragon Fitwear brand.  I am no longer a sponsored athlete as they have discontinued the sponsorship program, but I&amp;#39;m applying to continue on as a Brand Ambassador with Paragon!&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Who is Paragon Fitwear?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paragon Fitwear is a fitness clothing company.  Their products are of high quality and are a mixture of cotton and spandex, giving the clothes a light, airy, and stretchy feel.  Also, the clothes are an athletic fit/cut meaning that they extend a few inches longer on the torso.  This helps when working out so that your shirt doesn&amp;#39;t ride up and expose your rock hard abs ;) haha!!! Another nice thing about the shirts are that they are tapered so that the torso hugs the lats and tapers down near the waist to add to the illusion of being slim.  I recently picked up a stringer as well and those fit nicely, similar to the shirts just without sleeves essentially.  I hope to try the joggers soon, once I get a hold of them I&amp;#39;ll review them, too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;&amp;quot;Hey Jack! Where can I get some clothes?&amp;quot;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well I&amp;#39;m glad you asked!!! &lt;a href=&quot;http://paragonfitwear.com?rfsn=134828.6de5d&quot;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt; to check out Paragon&amp;#39;s website!!! Take a look around and see if you can find something you like!  If you have any questions feel free to contact them or shoot me a tweet &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/torchyhd&quot;&gt;@torchyhd&lt;/a&gt;!!! I respond to both tweets and DM&amp;#39;s! And if you do decide to pick up any dope clothes be sure to upload them and tag myself and Paragon in the photo so we can see what you liked!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks again for checking out my blog! I hope you enjoyed this post and I will see you in the next one!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://scontent-lax3-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xpa1/t31.0-8/12087165_10206300700729554_9161392165512389853_o.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SponsorPic&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://jackalvarez.me/2015/10/21/Paragon/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jackalvarez.me/2015/10/21/Paragon/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>About Me</category>
        
        <category>Paragon Fitwear</category>
        
        <category>Fitness</category>
        
        <category>Athlete</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My First Blog!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi there! Thanks for checking out my website! I like to think of this site as my little outlet to talk about myself and document my experiences and thoughts! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To continue on from what was said on the front page, I come from California. Sunny San Diego! America&amp;#39;s Finest City! I lived there all my life leading up to my departure off to college.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of my hobbies include: playing video games, making YouTube videos, and weightlifting (specifically powerlifting).  I play almost all kinds of video games, but my &amp;quot;specialty&amp;quot; is definitely FPS.  If you want to take a look at my YouTube videos, &lt;a href=&quot;http://youtube.com/torchyhd&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;! I can talk a lot about lifting, so I think I will leave that to my next blog post!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I really have no idea how to blog, and since my intention was just to get a first blog post up I think I will end this entry here.  In the future I will try to either blog about my &amp;quot;Day In The Life&amp;quot; or simply about a topic I feel like talking about!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for taking the time to read this post! See you in the next one!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://jackalvarez.me/2015/10/15/First-Blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jackalvarez.me/2015/10/15/First-Blog/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>About Me</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
